Carol: Hello? Tony?
Tony: Oh, hi, darling. How’s Zurich?
Carol: Fine, fine. I’m staying in a nice hotel – but it’s raining.
Can you hear it?
Tony: Yes, yes, I can.
Carol: How are the children?
Tony: Oh, they’re fine.
Carol: Where are they? What are they doing?
Tony: Lily’s in the living room. She’s doing her homework.
Carol: And Matt and Josh?
Tony: They’re in their bedroom. They’re reading.
Carol: I think I can hear them. Are you sure they’re reading?
Tony: Yes, yes. That noise is the TV.
Your mother’s watching a film.
Carol: What about you? Are you OK?
Tony: I’m fine. I’m making dinner – fish and vegetables.
Carol: Oh, great! Very healthy.
OK darling, I need to go now. See you on Tuesday.
Tony: Have a good day tomorrow. Bye.